{
    "id": "e4e3a7d2efac4ac6bdce3e65f5014291",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She accused me ………………. stealing her watch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am afraid ………………… cockroaches.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "from",
                "of",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She left the firm because she could not agree ………………. their policies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you angry ………………. me?",
            "description": "Both 'at' and 'with' are possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is anxious ……………….. an end to this misunderstanding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You must apologize …………………. disturbing him.",
            "description": "We apologize for something.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You must apologize ………………. your colleagues.",
            "description": "We apologize to somebody for something. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We arrived ………………. Budapest in the evening.",
            "description": "Both 'at' and 'in' are possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not very good ……………… badminton.",
            "description": "We use good at, bad at, clever at etc.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you believe ……………… life after death?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}